https://www.solent-events.co.uk/general/privacy-policy/

Skip to Navigation
Skip to Content
COVID-19 Update. Now operating as usual.
email us
Keep it social...
Menu
share
GENERAL
Privacy Policy
Solent Events is committed to protecting your privacy and has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website at URL: www.solent-events.co.uk.
01590 674900
Privacy Policy
Solent Events is committed to protecting your privacy and has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the website at URL: www.solent-events.co.uk.
Privacy Policy in brief
Solent Events does not disclose visitors’ information to third parties.
Any information that you provide us with, whether it be business or personal information (such as your name or address), cannot be seen by third parties. This site may at times contain links to other, third party websites; Solent Events is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
This privacy statement is not presented as a legally binding contract.
Privacy Policy in detail: Information we collect and use
There are sections in our website where we may ask you to register in order to gain access to high value documents, or to be able to download various items, or to make contact with Solent Events. Any information you provide will remain the secured property of Solent Events. Under no circumstances will it be sold or rented to any third party. Solent Events may, however, use your contact information to send you any information you have specifically requested or any other information or news about our company and services. Your details maybe used in an aggregated form for marketing analysis of our website traffic.
In addition to any personal information you may provide, Solent Events may, on occasion use software or other tools that enable the collection of relevant technical information, for example the IP address (Internet protocol) (IP), the operating system deployed on your computer, the browser used for access, various traffic patterns, as well as the address of any referring websites. Solent Events always traces how a visitor arrives at the Solent Events website, however we will not attempt to gather information from websites that you have visited prior to visiting the Solent Events website.
Use of personal information
Solent Events may use your personal information for the following purposes:
To enable you to use the site without repeatedly entering passwords or logins.
To provide information or services that you have requested.
To help us manage our content to ensure it is relevant and appropriate to you.
To alert you to company news, product upgrades, other updated information and new products and services from Solent Events.
Hyperlinks to other websites:
Solent Events may provide links on our site that direct to external, third party websites.
We have no control over the content other sites, nor the usage of information they gather.
We recommend that you always review the privacy policies at any third party sites you visit; they may not follow the same policies as us.
Opting out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.
This site gives users the following options to discontinue receiving future communications by any of the following means:
Send an e-mail to our client services team indicating your request to be unsubscribed from a specific list.
In writing to: Client Services, Unit 6 Dell Buildings, Milford Road, Lymington, Hampshire, SO41 OED
You can call our client services team on this telephone number: 01590 676599
Google Analytics
The Solent Events website uses cookies to allow Google Analytics to function correctly. Google Analytics is a free web analytics tools that helps us understand how visitors engage with the Solent Events website. These cookies have names that begin with __utm such as __utma and __utmz.
Google Analytics collects information anonymously; it reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. The cookies store information such as the number of visits to the website and what site referred the visitor to the web page. We use the information to view reports about how visitors interact with the website and to help us improve the website. A different set of cookies is used for each website, and visitors are not tracked across multiple sites.
Information about these cookies and how to reject or delete them: http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html and to opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Google’s privacy policy: http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html
How to control and delete cookies
You may restrict or block the cookies which are set by the Solent Events website, or any other website, through your browser settings. To find out more about cookies and how to manage them, visit www.aboutcookies.org.
Please be aware that restricting cookies may impact on the functionality of the Solent Events website.
April 2018
Get in touch with Solent Events
Do you have an event in mind? Send us your details using the form below or have a quick chat with one of our experts on. 01590 674900.
Our privacy policy
Call us now on 01590 674900 to discuss your next exhilarating water based event
©
Solent Events | Sitemap | Privacy Policy | Cookies | Links | Pricing | Blog
Unit 6a Dell Buildings,
Milford Road, Lymington,
Hampshire SO41 0ED
Site by Clear Signal
This website uses cookies. By continuing to use the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies.
CloseI agree
Return to the Top of the Page
